Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  - Subject Files, 1963-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accessions UA95-58, UA95-80, UA95-113, UA95-114, UA96-30, UA96-77, and UA97-65.
    - Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts & Science, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 82)
    - Unanswered, undated (Box 82)
    - United Way, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Club (Tom Stone), 1987 Feb.-1989 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Council on Water Resources, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Relations, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Relations: Leonard Pardue, 1987 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Relations: Green, William, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Relations Candidates: Green Replacement, 1986-1987 (Box 82)
    - University Relations Search, 1989 Aug.-1990 Aug. (Box 82)
    - University Research Association, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 82)
    - University Secretary, undated (Box 82)
    - University Union, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 82)
    - Urban Land Institute, 1986 June-1989 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Werber, William, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Werber, William M., 1986 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 83)
    - White, Richard: Dean of Arts & Sciences, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 83)
    - White, Richard: Dean of Arts & Sciences, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Women's Center, 1988-1993 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Women's Studies Program, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 83)
    - Women's Studies Program: Jean O'Barr, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 83)
  - Subject Files, 1964-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accession A2004-28.
    Files are arranged, for the most part, first alphabetically and then in reverse chronological order with some deviations.
    - AIDS, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - AT&T, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Abele, Julian, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Academic Priorities Committee, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Accounting Operations, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Accreditation, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Budget, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast 92/93, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30) (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Forecast, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Indirect Costs FY 91/92, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Reserve Funds, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: University Operations, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Year-End, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Adcock, John F.: Year-End 1990/91, 1991 May 1-1992 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Admissions 1993, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Admissions: Future, 1990 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 84)
    - Admissions: Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Admissions: Professional Schools, 1992 Sept. 1 -1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Admissions & Financial Aid Committee (Provost), 1986 Oct. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1991 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Aging And Human Development, Center For The Study Of, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - AIESEC (International Association Of Students In Economics & Commerce, 1986 Oct. 1-1991 Sept. 30 (Box 85)
    - Akzo, 1987 Mar. 1-1987 Oct. 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Affairs: Funderburk, Laney, 1987 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Affairs: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Affairs Survey Committee, 1991 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Award, Distinguished, 1986 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Class Reunions, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Alumni Magazine, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Airlines, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Association Of University Professors, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Association For The Advancement Of Science, 1985 Nov. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Council On Education, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Council Of Learned Societies, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Dance Festival, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - American Recording Orchestra, 1989 July 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 85)
    - American Tobacco, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Amoco Foundation, 1985 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Ampligen, 1987 Apr. 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 85)
    - Animal Rights, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 85)
    - Annenberg, Walter, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Annual Report, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Anthropology Department, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Applicants For Jobs, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Appointments, Promotions, And Tenure (AP&T), 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Architect, University, 1991 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Archives, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Art Department, 1985 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Arts, Institute Of, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Arts & Sciences Council, 1991 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Arts, Masters In, 1987 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Art Museum, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Art Museum Director Search Committee, 1986 Jan. 1-1986 Dec. 31 (Box 86)
    - Art Museum: Advisory Board, 1988 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Art Museum: Architectural & Site Committee, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Asian/Pacific Studies, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Associated Students Of Duke University, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Association Of American Colleges, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 86)
    - Association Of American Universities, 1993 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Association Of American Universities, 1992 July 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 87)
    - Association Of American Universities: Undergraduate Education Task Force, 1990 Apr. (Box 87)
    - Association Of Governing Boards, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: All American Bowl, 1989 Nov. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Atlantic Coast Conference, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Atlantic Coast Conference: ACC CEO Meeting, 1992 Sept. 17-1992 Sept. 18 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Baseball, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Butters, Tom, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: College Football Association, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: DUAA/HPER Merger, 1986 Mar. 1-1986 Apr. 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Football, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: NCAA, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Olympic Sports Festival, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: 1992 U.S. Olympic Track and Field Trials, 1990 Mar. 1-1992 June 1 (Box 87)
    - Athletics: Soccer, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Auxiliaries, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Awards: Charles A. Dukes, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 87)
    - Development: Annual Giving, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development Calendar, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Centurions, Duke 2000: The Society Of, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Office of Corporate Relations (M. Rierson), 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Durham-Duke Campaign, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Feasibility Study, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Foundation Relations (Linda Gerber), 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Gerber, Linda-Director of Development, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Gift Records, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: James B. Duke Society, 1992 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development, University: Miscellaneous, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: John Piva, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: President's Council, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Prospect/Clearance List, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Duke Seminar, 1985 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Duke Sowers, 1986 Feb. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Development: Barbara Smith, Assistant Director of Development, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Babcock Foundation, Mary Reynolds, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Barber, James David, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Battle, Joseph, 1985 July 1-1991 Aug. 31 (Box 88)
    - Benefits & Records Administration, 1986 Jan. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Biddle Foundation, Mary Duke, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Bishop Estate, 1986 Dec. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 88)
    - Black Employees, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Black Employees, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bloom, Robert H., 1984 Jan. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Board Room: Allen Building, 1985 July 1-1981 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Boards Of Visitors: Miscellaneous, 1965 July 1-1984 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bond Issues, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Botany Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bramberg, R. William, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Brooke, Harrison, 1986 July 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 89)
    - Bryan Center: Miscellaneous, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bryan, Joseph M., 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bryan Neurobiology Research Building, 1990 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Burke, Dolores: Opportunity Development Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Burlington Industries, 1986 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Burness, John: Senior Vice President For Public Affairs, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Burroughs Corporation, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Bursar's Office, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Calder Foundation, 1986 Dec. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Calendar, Academic, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Cameron, E. M., 1986 Jan. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Campus Club, 1983 Jan. 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 89)
    - Canadian Studies, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Career Development Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 89)
    - Carter, Rosalyn: Chair In Research & Mental Health, Emory University, 1985 July 1-1985 Nov. 15 (Box 89)
    - Cassidy & Associates, 1987 June 1-1989 Aug. 31 (Box 90)
    - Centennial Convocation, 1992 Mar. 1-1992 Oct. 31 (Box 90)
    - C.H.A.N.C.E., 1985 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chanticleer, 1985 July 1-1988 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chapel, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chapel Development Committee, 1980 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chartwell, 1993 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chemistry Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Christmas Party, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Chronicle, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Classical Studies Department, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Clippings, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Cogan, Marshall, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - Coles, Robert, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - College Entrance Exam Board, 1978 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 90)
    - College Foundation, 1976 July 1-1985 Sept. 30 (Box 90)
    - Commencement, 1994 (Box 90)
    - Commencement Committee, 1994 (Box 90)
    - Commencement, 1993 (Box 90)
    - Commencement Committee, 1993 (Box 90)
    - Commencement, 1992 (Box 90)
    - Commencement Committee, 1992 (Box 90)
    - Commencement, 1991 (Box 91)
    - Commencement Committee, 1991 (Box 91)
    - Commencement-Names For Future Speakers, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Commencement Task Force, 1989 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Commonwealth Fund, The, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Communications, Center For The Study Of, 1986 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Community Relations, 1987 Jan. 1-1988 Sept. 30 (Box 91)
    - Community Service Center, 1988 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Computer Assistance Language Instruction (COLOE), 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Computer Camp (Duck), 1986 May 1-1987 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Computer Science Department, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Computer Services, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Conflict Of Interest, Ad Hoc Committee, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Consortium On Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1993 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Consortium On Financing Higher Education (COFHE), 1991 July 1-1992 Dec. 31 (Box 91)
    - Continuing Education-Judith Ruderman, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Cool Summit, 1987 June 1-1987 Aug. 31 (Box 91)
    - Council For Advancement And Support Of Education (CASE), 1976 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Council On Postsecondary Accreditation, 1985 July 1 (Box 91)
    - Council Of Southern Universities, 1983 (Box 91)
    - Counseling And Psychological Services (CAPS), 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Cultural Affairs, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Curriculum, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Dalton, Henry, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Dana Foundation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Davis, Chuck, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Day Care, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - De Rothschild, Maurice, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Deane Institute, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Deans Council And Officers Meeting, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Deaths, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 91)
    - Deferred Maintenance, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Dey, K. V. R., 1986 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Distinguished Professors, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Diversity Awareness Program, Committee to Study, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Divinity School, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Divinity School-Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Divinity-Review of Dean Campbell 91/92, 1991 Nov. 1-1992 Mar. 31 (Box 92)
    - Dixon, Tom, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Documentary Studies, Center For, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Dowell, Earl, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Downhower, Laura, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Drama Advisory Board, 1988 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Drill, Isobel Craven, 1987 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke, Angier B., 1980 Jan. 1-1988 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke, A. B. Scholars Program, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke, B. N. Leadership Program, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Dialogue, 1986 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke, Doris, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Endowment: Appropriations, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Endowment: Committee On Educational Institutions, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Endowment: Medical Center, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Endowment: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 92)
    - Duke Endowment: Nanaline H. Duke Fund, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke Endowment: Proposals, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke Endowment: Trustees of The Duke Endowment, 1979 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke Experience Survey, 1986 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke Family, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke Gardens, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Duke, Short History Of, 1970-1988 Dec. 31 (Box 93)
    - Dupont, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham Arts Council, 1985 Dec. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham Chamber Of Commerce, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham, City Of, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham City Schools, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham County General Hospital, 1986 Jan. (Box 93)
    - Durham Morning Herald, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Durham, University of, 1985 Jan. 1 (Box 93)
    - Durham War on Drugs, 1989 July 1-1989 Sept. 30 (Box 93)
    - East Campus, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - East-West Trade Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Economics Department, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Edgerton, N. Edward, 1987 Mar. 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 93)
    - Education Program, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Educational Assistance Program, 1985 July 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 93)
    - Edwards, Ben, 1988 Mar. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Endowment Funds, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Endowment Growth, 1982 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 93)
    - Engineering NSF/ERC Proposal, 1989 July 1 (Box 94)
    - Engineering School, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Engineering School-Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Engineering School-Deans Council, 1989 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Engineering-Review of Dean Dowell, 1991-1992, 1991 Nov. 1-1992 Apr. 30 (Box 94)
    - English Department, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Environment, School of the, 1992 Sept. 1 -1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Environment, School of the: Board Of Visitors, 1992 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Exxon Foundation: Gifts & Grants, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Facilities Planning Management, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1 992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Faculty-Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Faculty-New Arts & Sciences, 1984 Dec. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Faculty Tuition Benefit, 1987 July 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 94)
    - Financial Aid Office, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Financial Aid: Jim Belvin, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Food Services, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Ford Foundation, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Ford National Review & Advisory Panel For Improving Campus Race Relations, 1990 Jan. 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 94)
    - Forest, Duke, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Forest, Duke, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 94)
    - Forest, Duke, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Forest, Duke, 1986 Jan. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Forest History Society, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, School Of, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Forlines, John A., Jr., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Founders' Day, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Founders' Society, 1988 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fraternities-Sororities, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Freshman Parties, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Freshman Seminar Program, 1974 Jan. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fringe Benefit Office, 1986 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fulbright Fellowships, 1985 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuller, Peyton, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuqua, J. B., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuqua School Of Business, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuqua School: Board Of Visitors, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuqua School-Soviet Program, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Fuqua Thomas Center, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 95)
    - Gates, Henry, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gates, Henry, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gates, Henry, 1986 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gay/Lesbian Task Force, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Geller, Dr. George R., 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - General Electric Foundation, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - General Mills Foundation, 1986 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Geology Department, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - German/American Relations, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Germanic Languages Department, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gifts & Grants: Bequests, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gifts & Grants: Foundations-Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gifts & Grants: Individuals, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gifts & Grants: Scholarships, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 96)
    - Gifts & Grants: Hewlett Foundation, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Glaxo, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Golden Key National Honor Society 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Gonzales, Felipe, 1986 (Box 97)
    - Goodwin, Craufurd, 1986 May 1-1987 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Gorter Endowment, 1988 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Government Relations, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Government Relations: PCAST Conference, 1992 July 21 (Box 97)
    - Governors Center, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Grace Foundation, 1989 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Graduate School: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Graduate School, Search For Dean Of, 1991 Mar.-1991 July (Box 97)
    - Graduate & Professional Student Council, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Greater Triangle Community Foundation, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Griffith, William, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip (Provost), 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Gross Fund, 1986 June 1-1986 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation: John Simon, 1986 Jan. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Haltom, Allison, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Hamner, W. Clay, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Hayti Development Corporation, 1985 Dec. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Henderson, R. James, 1985 Mar. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 97)
    - Hillerbrand, Dr. Hans: Acting Dean Of Faculty Of Arts & Sciences, 1990 July 1-1991 Aug. 31 (Box 98)
    - History Department, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1993 (Box 98)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1992 (Box 98)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Honorary Degrees: Miscellaneous, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Honorary Degrees: Names For Future Reference, 1982 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Hotel/Conference Center Downtown, 1982 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Housing Concerns, 1990 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - How to Think Straight, 1985 July 1-1985 Sept. 30 (Box 98)
    - Human Resources: Kahr, Toby, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Human Resources: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Infrastructure, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - ITT, 1986 July 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 98)
    - Insurance, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Internal Audit, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Affairs, Masters In, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Agreements, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Association of Universities, 1984 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Business Machines, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Development Research, Center of (CIDR), 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - International Studies: Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Investment Office, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Invitations Declined, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Islamic & Arabian Development Studies, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 98)
    - Jazz Institute, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Job Enhancement, 1987 July 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 99)
    - Job Openings: Other Colleges & Universities, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Johnson, Robert Wood Foundation, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Judaic Studies, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Keck Foundation, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Kelley, Allen, 1986 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)
    - Kenan Trust, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 99)